

# Contácto

#### Tel

+54 9 11 6170-2233

## **Email**

zackmango@gmail.com

## **Address**

Paraná 3257, Martinez,

Buenos Aires, Argentina

Scrum

Canva

SASS

Photoshop

Illustrator

# Habilidades

- HTML5
  - ....
- CSS
- Javascript
- React
- GIT
- APIs
- VSCode
- Bootstrap

# **Habilidades Blandas**

- Communication
- Problem-solving
- Interpersonal relationships
- Self-learning
- Responsibility
- Time management
- Teamwork
- Organization
- Leadership
- Negotiation

# **Idiomas**

- Español nativo
- Inglés B1

# References

- Pascual D. Lima, Domo Sur Managing Partner, Tel: +54 9 11 5884
  3769.
- Nahuel Pena, Devir Arg -Administration, Tel: +54 9 11 5884 3760.

# FEDERICO M. STEMPLER

# FRONT FND DEVELOPER

# **About**

I am a passionate Front-end Developer with skills to find simple solutions to complex problems. I have led teams in innovative projects across various fields and have over 4 years of experience in digital marketing consulting. Currently, I am embarking on a path of independent development in the world of Front-end Development, with a great capacity for learning and enjoying creative and collaborative environments.

## **EDUCATION**

- Apps Developer Certification (Ongoing) Coderhouse - Jan 2023
- Front End Developer Certification
  Coderhouse Aug 2023
- Marketing Developer Certification
  WOW Marketing & Comunicación Agu 2020
- Digital Marketing Developer Certification WOW Marketing & Comunicación - Jun 2020

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## React Js Project - Spin City Records | Coderhouse | aug 2023

- HTML | CSS React
- Node.Js
- JS Bootstrap Firebase

## **Javascript Project - Music Pal**

Coderhouse | jun 2023

- Frontend Development
- JS Development
- API Chat Gpt Development

## **Web Developing Project - The Jazz Guide**

Coderhouse | jan to oct 2023

- Frontend Development
- HTML | CSS | SASS | GIT

## **CAROESTA.COM Development**

## April 2023

- Tienda Nube
- E-Commerce
- HTML | CSS

## **Digital Marketing Consultant Freelance**

# Sep 2021 - Ongoing

- Strategy Development
- Content planning
- Content developing

## **Account Manager**

## WOW Marketing & Comunicación | Agu 2020 - Sep 2021

- · Account managing
- Content Development
- Strategy development
- Reporting and Results Presentation
- Ads strategy and development

## **Sales Manager**

## Devir Argentina | Mar 2017 - Jun 2020

- Implementation and development of sales tactics and strategies.
- Sales planning
- Reporting
- Purchases plans
- New bussiness opportunity development

## **Account Manager**

Domo Sur | Mar 2010 - Feb 2017